{"data":[{"question":"Brenda was born _____ the fourth of July.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"2"},{"question":"I thought we were going to be late, but we arrived at the concert _____ time.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"2"},{"question":"The expiration date is printed _____ the bottom of the box.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"2"},{"question":" I like to go skiing _____ winter.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"2"},{"question":"I'm starting my new job ______ 7 June.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"2"},{"question":"The situation has been better _____ the telecommunications industry.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"2"},{"question":"We haven't seen that kind of economic growth _____ a decade.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"2"},{"question":"An accident can happen _____ a split second.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"2"},{"question":"Dieter went to the cinema _____ Monday.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"2"},{"question":"My children are _____ home.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"2"}]}